Milton R. Konvitz Additional Papers /4085
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
  - "Censorship" and "Uniformity and Nonconformity" (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - MRK Papers (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Human Rights and Judaism (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Dropsie University (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - MRK Papers (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Melville Society Extracts (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "The Rule of Law" (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Notes (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Subject Files & Correspondence (Box 11)
  - Labor-Related Articles (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Civil Liberties-Related Articles (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Immigration (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Supreme Court Articles (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bork-Related Articles (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - First Annual Lawyer Convention of the Federalist Society (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Judaism Part 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Judaism Part 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Policy-Related Articles and Essays Part 1 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Policy-Related Articles and Essays Part 2 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Cornell-Related Documents (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - misc. Notes, Letters, and Magazines (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Office File Clippings (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Publications (Box 12)
  - "Jews and the New Orleans Economic and Social Elites" - Fishman and Zweigenhaft (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - "Early Caribbean Jewry: A Demographic Perspective" - Cohen (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - "Mainstream" Jan. 1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - ILR: "Labor Law Research Project" - Landis and Rosenzweig (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - "Look at Latin America" - The Foreign Policy Association (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - "Encounter" Oct. 1960 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "The Origins and Constitutionality of Limitations on Truth as a Defense in Tort Law" - Franklin (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - "Man and Machine in the Search for Justice" - Stone (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Association of American Law School "Journal of Legal Education" (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - "Criminal Justice Ethics" - Winter/Spring 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - "New Sources of Information on Eastern European Jewish Life, 1785-1920" - Uchitelle (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - New York University Law Review April 1968 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "Zionism and Jewish Education" - The Pedagogic Reporter Winter 1979 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Doctoral Dissertations and Master's Theses Accepted by American Institutions of Higher Learning, 1967-68 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Index on Censorship January 1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - The Jewish Theological Seminary of America Commencement Exercises - June 4, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - The Jewish Theological Seminary of America Commencement Exercises - June 4, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Pensee: Student Academic Freedom Forum - Velikovsky (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Pensee: Student Academic Freedom Forum - Velikovsky (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - "Midstream" March 1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - "Midstream" December 1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - "The State of Civil Rights: 1977" (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Academe - January/February 1982 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - "Cornell Law Forum" February 1981 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - ILR Report Fall 1981 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Humanist Manifestos 1 and 2 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - "Freedom of Assembly: A Defense Digest" (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - "The Right of Assembly" - Fennell (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - "Reasonable Restrictions Upon Freedom of Assemblage" - Roe (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - "Freedom of Assembly and Anti-Democratic Groups" (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Hardyman v. Collins Brief for the American Jewish Congress (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - "The Right of Assembly" - Fennell (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - SCOPUS - Fall 1980 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - "As I Remember" - Kellett (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - "The Continuing Zionist Revolution" - Ankori (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - "Encyclopedia of Human Ideas on Ultimate Reality and Meaning" - Horvath (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - "The Life and Times of a Jewish Victorian" - Temkin (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - "1966 and All That! Loosing the Chains of Precedent" - Stone (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - "Stand Up and be Counted" - Stone (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - "Research for Advancement of Peace" - Stone (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - "No Peace-No War In the Middle East" - Stone (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - "Approaches to the Notion of International Justice" - Stone (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - "The 'November Resolution' and Middle East Peace: Pitfall of Guidepost?" - Stone (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - "Equity for Cities in School Finance Reform" (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - "History of Religion: Judaism at Brown University in Practice and in Theory" (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - "Statements and Documents on the October 1973 War" (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - "Sadat's Strategy" - Eidelberg (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Harvard Civil Rights: Civil Liberties Law Review January 1973 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - The Columbia Survey of Human Rights Law (1967-68) (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - "Human Rights" Summer 1973 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - "Human Rights" Fall 1973 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - "Human Rights" - Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Cornell University Policy Notebook for Students, Faculty and Staff - August 1980 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - The Yale Law Journal - March 1975 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - "The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science" - May 1967 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - "Conservative Judaism" - Winter 1969 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - "Conservative Judaism" - Winter 1969 (Copy 2) (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations Review January 1968 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations Review October 1967 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations Review 1966-67 - Horton (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - The African Studies Review Vol. XXIII, No. 1 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - University Faculty and Faculty Council of Representatives for 1979-80 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - "International Commission of Jurists" - MacDermot (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Cornell International Law Journal 1972 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - International Commission of Jurists June 1978 - MacDermot (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - University Faculty and Faculty Council of Representatives 1980-81 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Proceedings and Addresses of the American Philosophical Association November 1981 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - University Faculty and Faculty Council of Representatives 1978-79 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Memorial Statements Cornell University Faculty (1978-79) (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Publications (Box 13)
  - "Hebraic Foundations of American Democracy" - Katsh (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - "The Work Ethic - A Critical Analysis" - Barbash, Lampman, Levitan, Tyler (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - "Fascism Democracy and the Press" - Martin (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "Freedom of Speech and of the Press" - Holmes (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Jews, Zionism, and South Africa" - Abramowitz (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - "Freedom of the Press - Personal Liberty or Property Liberty" - Snyder (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - "Liberty of the Press" - Studebaker (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - "Maimon and Maimonides" - Atlas (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "Dissent: A Culture in Torment" - Weiss (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "Sovyetish Heymland" - Brumberg (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - "The Spirit of Prayer" - Heschel (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - "The Legal Position of the Jews in the Soviet Union" - Korey (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - "Symposium: My Jewish Affirmation" 1961 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - "Symposium: My Jewish Affirmation" (2nd Copy) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - "Solomon Maimon's Doctrine of Infinite Reason and its Historical Relations" - Atlas (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - The Reconstructionist October 1952 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - "Toward a Guide for Jewish Ritual Usage" (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - "Hebrew Begins Here" - Sarlin (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Report on the Jewish Community Relations Agencies (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Industrial Bulletin June 1967 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - The American Federationist July 1967 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - The American Federationist September 1967 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - The American Federationist September 1967 (2nd Copy) (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - The American Federationist August 1967 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - The American Federationist October 1968 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - "The Death of a Newspaper: The Story of the Detroit Times" - Ferman (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - NYS: Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations Interim Report June 17,1968 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - "Decline of Labor Union Power" August 1960 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - "Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959" (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - The Story of the Jewish Agency for Israel (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Jerusalem before the United Nations (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - "Individuals' Procedure Rights in Union Disciplinary Actions" - Smythe, Schwab, Madigan (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - "Labor Leader 1860's" - Richardson (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - "Social Action" (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - John Dewey at Ninety (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - The Substance of American Fair Employment Practices Legislation I: Employers (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - "In Search of Maturity in Industrial Relations" (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - "A New Philosophy for Labor" - Tyler (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - NYS Governor's ' Committee on Public Employee Relations Final Report 1966 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - NYS Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations Final Report (2nd Copy) (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Institute of Industrial Relations - Prasow and Peters (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Book in Yiddish (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - "The Jewish People" - Shaprio (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - "The Jewish Intellectual" (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Round Table: A Free and Responsible Press (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Charles Pierce (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - "Religion and Society in Ancient Judaism" - Neusner (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - "Judaism and Human rights" - Shestack (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - "Hagar and Ishmael: A Study in Arab-Jewish Relations" - Eichhorn (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Town Meeting: December 15,1941 from Columbia University Press (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - "Jewish Humor" - Grossman (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - "The Jewish Intellectual" (2) (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - "The Jewish Intellectual" (3) (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - "The Jewish Intellectual" (4) (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - "The Jewish Intellectual" (5) (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Growth of Labor Law in the United States (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - "American Interests in the Middle East" - Hall and Voss (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Anglo-American Committee of Inquiry (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - "Mediterranean Pact and Near East Security" - Patch (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - "Immigration to Palestine" - Brewer (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - "East and West of Suez" - Badeau (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - "Israel's Needs and Our Responsibilities" - Keyserling (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - "Whose Promised Lands?" (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - The Arabs in Israel (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - "What is a Jew?" (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - "American Jews: Their Story" - Handlin (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - The Riverton Study - Sklare and Vosk (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - NLRB v. Fleetwood Trailer Co., Inc. (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - "Toward Collective Bargaining in Non-Profit Hospitals: Impact of New York Law" - Gamm (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - "Year One of the Taylor Law" (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - NYS Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations Interim Report 1968 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Innovation in Collective Bargaining - Young (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - "Legislation by Collective Bargaining" (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Brief History of the American Labor Movement (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - "Toward a New Constitutional Status for Labor Unions: A Proposal" - Malick (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - "Theories of the Labor Movement" - Taft (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - "The Role of the State in Collective Bargaining" - Shister (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - "Union Constitutions" - Bromwich (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - "The Decline of the Labor Movement" - Barkin (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - The Employment Act of 1946 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - "The Outlook for Union Growth" - Shister (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Labor Monopoly Policy Reconsidered - Rottenberg (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Basic Problems of Plantation Labour (Box 13, Folder 83)
- Publications; Milton Konvitz Lecture notes (2) (some from NYU and Cornell) (Box 14)
  - "Cases and Materials on Labor Law" - Handler and Hays (1 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - "Cases and Materials on Labor Law" - Handler and Hays (2 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - "Cases and Materials on Labor Law" - Handler and Hays (3 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - "Collective Bargaining: Labor Relations Law and Legislation" - Konvitz (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - General Notes (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Publications; Milton Konvitz Lecture notes (1) (some from NYU and Cornell) (Box 15)
  - Milton Konvitz Notebooks Part 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Milton Konvitz Notebooks Part 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Milton Konvitz Notebooks Part 3 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Milton Konvitz Notebooks Part 4 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - "Restrictive Work Rules: Their Legal Aspects" - Cheek (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Milton Konvitz - Forest Home, Ithaca, NY (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - American Ideals (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Legal Thought - Milton Konvitz (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Report on Human Rights in El Salvador - July 20, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Russia Since Stalin: Old Trends and New Problems - January 1956 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - The Soviet Union Since WWII - May 1949 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Kallen (Box 16)
  - Bernard Semel Award to Professor Horace Kallen (1956) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - United Jewish Appeal of Greater NY pays tribute to Dr. Horace Kallen - March, 24, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Golden Jubilee Award to Professor Horace Kallen - January 26, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Picture of Professor Horace Kallen (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - PLEA Bargaining: A Game of Criminal Justice (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Picture (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Publications; Miscellaneous (esp. Jewish Studies) (Box 17)
  - Survey of Formal University Jewish Studies Programs in the World Today (July 1973) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Studies Part 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Studies Part 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Studies Part 3 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Studies Part 4 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - University Teaching of Jewish Civilization - Moshe Davis (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - American Doctoral Dissertations and Master's Theses on Jewish Subjects 1970-72 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report 1975: Carnegie Corporation of New York (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Judaism and Universities (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Jewish Studies (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Colure: Report of Committee on Fellowships and Scholarships (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture: The Fellowship Program, 1965-73 - A Preliminary Analysis (Copy 1) (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture: The Fellowship Program, 1965-73 - A Preliminary Analysis (Copy 2) (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture: Survey of Formal University Jewish Studies (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture: Introductory Statement for Commission on Formal University Jewish Studies Programs - Konvitz (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture: Final Report of Commission on Formal University Jewish Studies (Copy 1) (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture: Final Report of Commission on Formal University Jewish Studies (Copy 2) (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture: Final Report of Commission on Training Programs (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture: Appendix A (Recipients of Doctoral Scholarships, 1974-75) (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - International Studies and Judaism (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Pre-Doctoral Fellowships (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Fellowship and Scholarship Programs (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Konvitz and Fellowship Programs (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Grant Questions (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Fellowship and Independent Studies General (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Memorial Foundation - Responses to Commission Report (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Publications & Books (Box 18)
  - "Editor's Note" - Hanslowe, ILR Review, July 1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - "The Founding of the NYS School of Industrial and Labor Relations" - Konvitz (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - "Essays on the Occasion of the Seventieth Anniversary of The Dropsie University" (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Konvitz Mini-Essays (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - "Privacy and the Law: A Philosophical Prelude" - Konvitz, Spring 1966 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - "Whittling Away Religious Freedom" - Konvitz, Commentary, June 1946 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - "Biographical Introduction to Legal History and Ethnology" - Gilissen, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "An Empirical Theory of the Labor Movement: W. Stanley Jevons" - Konvitz, January 1948 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "What is Jewish Living?" - Konvitz, Judaism, January 1952 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "The Larger Vision" - Morris Raphael Cohen (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - "Profane Religion and Sacred Law" - Konvitz (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Congress Monthly - January 1979 and April 1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Louis D. Brandeis Article (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Emanuel Rackman and Creative Judaism (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - "Herman Melville in the Holy Land" - Konvitz, Midstream, December 1979 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University Fifth Summer Conference on International Law - June 18-20, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - General Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Junis Irving Scales v. US (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Raphael Konigsberg v. State Bar of California (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - "The Communist Conspiracy" - Part 1, Section A (Marxist Classics) (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - "The Communist Conspiracy" - Part 1, Section B (The USSR) (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - "The Communist Conspiracy" Part 1, Section C (World Congresses of the Communist International) (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - "The Communist Conspiracy" Part 1 Section D (Communist Activities Around the World) (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - "The Communist Conspiracy" Part 1 Section E (The Comintern and the CPUSA) (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - "Soviet Total War" Vol. 1 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - "Soviet Total War" Vol. 2 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Supreme Court of the US - October Term, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - In the Supreme Court - October Term 1950 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - "Civil Rights 1957" - Hearings Before the Subcommittee on Constitutional Rights (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Publications & Correspondence Files (Box 19)
  - Economic Opportunity Act of 1964, as Amended (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - "Implementation of the Final Act of the Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe" - Nov. 1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1967 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Salzburg Seminar North American Directory 1947-82) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - "Poverty and Minimum Living Standards: The Role of the ILO" (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Records 1981-82 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - The Institute for Advanced Study - Annual Report 1983/84 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - "The Right to Keep and Bear Arms" (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1967 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Cardozo Law Review Winter 1986 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Preliminary Draft of Proposed Bankruptcy Rules (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - South Texas Law Journal - Fall 1985 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Poverty Amid Plenty - The American Paradox (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Constitutional Commentary (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Improving the Public Welfare System (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - The Negro Family: The Case for National Action (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - The Social and Economic Status of Negros in the United State, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - The Journal of Law and Religion (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - "New Perspectives" (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Race and Desegregation (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Women and Unions (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - "Labor Management Committees: Confrontation, Cooptation, or Cooperation?" - Gold (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Boston Public Schools: Their Plight and Future (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - "USA in New Dimensions" (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - "Implementation of Helsinki Final Act" and "1982 Annual Report" (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - "A Short History of the Right to Petition Government for the Redress of Grievances" (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Cornell-Related (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - "The Question of Arbitrability" and "American Academy of Arts and Sciences" (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Law and Judaism (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Equity (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Jewish Studies (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - ILR Related (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - The Peace Movement (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Hebrew Culture Foundation (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Hebrew Culture Foundation Part 2 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Midstream (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Publications (Box 20)
  - Israel Essays (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Israel Pamphlets (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - "Israel Argosy" Vol. 3, 5, 6 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - "Israel Argosy" Vol. 7-9 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Books on the Middle East and Palestine (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - International General (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - International General (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - ILR Labor Law Research Project: " Some Aspects of Damage Suits Against Unions" - Landis (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Minority Parties and the Ballot (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Elections and Election Law (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Civil Liberties: Focus on the Press (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Political Action (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Christianity, Society, and Democracy (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Limitations of Liberty/Rights (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Clear and Present Danger (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Sedition (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Intergroup Relations (1965 and 1966) (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Koneping Book (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Subject Files, Correspondence, Publications, Current (Box 21)
  - Ethnic Separation Articles (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Catholicism (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Judaism (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Judaism (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The US and the World (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - International Relations (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Employee Relations and Law (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - "Academe" (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - American Civil Liberties Union Reports (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - American Civil Liberties (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Report of the ILR Review Panel - April 1987 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Milton Konvitz (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Konvitz ILR 300 Labor Relations: Law and Legislation Spring 1952 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Publications (civil rights) & Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Konvitz ILR 300 - Labor Relations: Law and Legislation Spring 1952 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Konvitz ILR 600 - Role of Government in Labor Relations Fall 1950 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Notes (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Notes (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Twenty Years After Brown: Equality of Educational Opportunity (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - The Federal Civil Rights Enforcement Effort - 1974 Vol. V (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - The Federal Civil Rights Enforcement Effort - 1974 Vol. VI (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - The Crew Size Dispute in the Railroad Industry (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - United States Commission on Civil Rights (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Anti-Semitism (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - "Truce of Dialogue?: American Catholic Attitudes Towards the Jews, 1945-76" - Singer (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - "Prophet's and Priests in Israel's Technological Development" - Keren (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - "The Agricultural Character of Jewish Settlement in the Negev" - Kark (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - "On Perverse Suburbanization: The Case of Jerusalem" - Plaut (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - "Measure" - July 1986 (Box 22, Folder 15)